Finding Aid for the Sol Babitz Papers PASC-M.0052
UCLA Library Special Collections
Sol Babitz papers
1948-1982
UCLA Library Special Collections
Babitz, Sol
PASC-M.0052
35.5 Linear Feet (71 boxes)
7 Audiovisual Carriers (7 records)
This collection consists of research notes, musical sketches, manuscripts, published scores, books, pamphlets, periodical issues, offprints, typed drafts of articles, photocopies of articles, scores, miscellaneous printed music pages, and correspondence.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942303443606533
Administrative/Biographical History
Babitz was born on Oct. 11, 1911, in Brooklyn, NY; he was largely a self-taught violinist since leaving high school; his violin teachers included Carl Flesch in Berlin and Marcel Chailley in Paris; his interest in performance practice was aroused by the writing of Arnold Dolmetsch and encouraged by Igor Stravinsky, whose string parts Babitz edited for many years; he was a violinist with the Los Angeles Philharmonic from 1933-37, and then played with Hollywood studio orchestras until 1952; editor, International musician (1941-62); co-founded the Early Music Laboratory (EML) in 1948; he devoted much of his research to the problems of performance practices in baroque and classical music through studying and interpreting 17th and 18th century treatises, and he incorporated his findings in recordings, articles, and bulletins; died in 1982.
Scope and Content
Research notes, manuscript and typed; musical sketches and manuscripts; published scores, books, pamphlets, periodical issues and offprints, with and without annotations; typed drafts of articles; photocopies of articles, scores, and miscellaneous printed music pages; and correspondence - all mostly related to baroque performance practice research done through the Early Music Laboratory (EML). Includes a set of EML Bulletins, other EML publications, and disc recordings of EML sponsored performances.
Musicologists -- United States -- Archives.; Performance practice (Music) -- Research.; Babitz, Sol -- Archives; Early Music Laboratory
- Manuscripts, ca. 1950-1980; Series 1.; 11 boxes (14.7 linear ft.)
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes Babitz transcriptions of works by Bach, Chabrier, Corelli, Dohnany, Fantana, Geminiani, Greshwin, Handel, Henebry, Josquin, Marais, Marini, Metteis, Mozart, Purcell, Spinacino, Stravinksy, Tappert/Lully, Walther, and unknown composers. The Handel Sonata IV contains a note for Einstein.
  - Transcriptions and Sketches, ca. 1940-1980; Subseries 1.; 6 boxes
    This sub-series consists of sketch books, solos of Bessie Smith, Duke Ellington, Joe Venuti, Sidney Bechet, Louis Armstrong, Brunskwick, Morton, from Okeh label and others.
    - Musical Sketches (Box 2)
    - Transcriptions (Box 2)
    - Manuscripts (Box 7)
    - Musical scores. (Box 65, Folder 1)
      Annotated published scores and methods books. Original manuscript scores with annotations.
    - Musical scores. (Box 67)
      Loose annotated music.
    - Musical scores. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Musical scores. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Musical Sketches (Box 72)
  - Unidentified Musical Works, ca. 1940-1980; Subseries 2.; 5 boxes (6.7 linear ft.)
    This series contains miscellaneous unidentified musical sketches and manuscripts. Xerox and photocopies of miscellaneous printed music pages. Ozalid copies of pages from miscellaneous works by unidentified composers.
    - Unidentified Musical Works (Box 1)
    - Misc. (Box 68)
      Loose leaf notebooks with pencil and ink entries, miscellaneous non-EML books and brochures, original manuscript scores, some with annotations.
    - Misc. (Box 69)
    - Misc. (Box 70)
    - Misc. (Box 71)
- Early Music Laboratory Bulletins and Management, 1948-1980; Series 2.; 22 boxes (29.5 linear ft.)
  This series consists of notes, mock-ups, off-prints, audio materials, typed drafts, and completed articles for the Early Music Laboratory Bulletin, published by Babitz.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO/AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audio materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
  - EML Bulletin, 1970-1972 (Box 3)
  - EML Bulletin, 1970-1974 (Box 4)
  - EML Bulletin, 1974-1980 (Box 5)
  - EML Bulletin, 1952-1978 (Box 6)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Research notes and papers, manuscript and typed. Offprints of published articles by various scholars. Various booklets, lectures, and brochures.
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - EML Bulletin, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Early music laboratory materials (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 13)
    Set of EML bulletins, and other EML publications. Disc recordings of EML sponsored performances. Xerox copies of music editions of early music works. Articles by Babitz and Boyden.
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 14)
  - Early music laboratory materials (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Set of EML bulletins, and other EML publications. Disc recordings of EML sponsored performances. Xerox copies of music editions of early music works. Additionally, in this box are 2 recordings of The Los Angeles Sax Quartet - The Art of the Fugue, and 3 recordings of The Future of Baroque Music, a lecture/demonstration by Sol Babitz.
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Set of EML bulletins, and other EML publications. Disc recordings of EML sponsored performances. Xerox copies of music editions of early music works.
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - EML Bulletin, ca. 1960s (Box 18)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Annotated volumes of EML publications, research notes and papers, manuscript and typed.
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - undated (Box 19)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Early musicl laboratory materials. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Early music laboratory materials. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - EML Bulletin, ca. 1970s (Box 36)
  - EML Bulletin, undated (Box 37)
  - EML Bulletin, 1952-1969 (Box 2)
  - Early Music Laboratory tape #3 (Box 89)
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO MATERIALS: audio/audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
  - EML research files (Box 8)
  - EML research files (Box 10)
  - Early music laboratory materials (Box 81)
- Sheet Music, ca. 1935-1975; Series 3.; 10 boxes (13.4 linear ft.)
  The series consists of annotated and blank original printed copies assorted sheet music. Included are works by composers such as Bach, Mestrino, anonymous Renaissance songs, Couperin L'Art de Toucher le Clavecin, Dolmetsch treatise, Mestrino, Kolem, Mozart, Selinsky, Warren, Purcell, Abdelazer, Dolmetsch, Dvorak, Stravinsky, and unknown composers.
  - Misc. music. (Box 57)
    Professional sheetmusic, scores, and parts for other people's music.
  - Musical scores. (Box 58)
    Annotated published scores and methods books. Annotated xerox and ozalid copies of scores.
  - Musical scores. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Musical scores. (Box 60)
  - Musical scores. (Box 61)
  - Musical scores. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Musical scores. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Musical scores. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Musical scores. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Musical scores. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Musical scores. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Musical scores. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Musical scores. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Musical scores. (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Musical scores. (Box 63)
    3 unnumbered folders containing Baroque repertoire in manuscript. Babitz hand and annotations.
  - Musical scores. (Box 64)
  - Musical scores. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Musical scores. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Musical scores. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Musical scores. (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Musical scores. (Box 66)
    1 envelope: Ives manuscripts (not originals)plus related correspondence.
- Research, 1947-1979; Series 4.; 10 boxes (13.4 linear ft.)
  This series consists of notes, articles, and sheet music used by Babitz for research of Baroque performance practices; See also Series 3 Early Music Laboratory Bulletins and Management.
  - Research materials (Box 11)
  - Research materials (Box 12)
  - Research materials (Box 13)
  - Research materials (Box 14)
  - Research materials (Box 16)
  - Research materials (Box 17)
  - Research materials (Box 21)
  - Research materials (Box 24)
  - Research materials (Box 25)
  - Research materials (Box 32)
  - Misc. (Box 51)
    General correspondence, research notes and papers.
- Sound Recordings, ca. 1950-1970; Series 5.; 5 boxes
  This series consists of 5" to 7" reel to reel sound recordings of Early Music Laboratory sponsored performances
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO MATERIALS: audio materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
  - Sound recordings, ca. 1950-1970; 5" and 10" reel-to-reel magnetic tape recordings (Box 40)
  - Sound recordings, ca. 1950-1970; 5" and 10" reel-to-reel magnetic tape recordings (Box 72)
  - Sound recordings, ca. 1950-1970; 5" and 10" reel-to-reel magnetic tape recordings (Box 74)
  - Sound recordings, ca. 1950-1970; 5" and 10" reel-to-reel magnetic tape recordings (Box 75)
  - Sound recordings, ca. 1950-1970; 5" and 10" reel-to-reel magnetic tape recordings (Box 76)
  - Sound Recordings, ca. 1950-1970 (Box 90)
  - Sound Recordings, ca. 1950-1970 (Box 91)
  - Sound recording, ca. 1950-1970 (Box 80)
  - Sound recordings, ca. 1950-1970 (Box 88)
- Books and Journals, ca. 1920-1975; Series 6.; 8 boxes (3.3 linear ft.)
  This series consists of various books and journals used by Babtiz in his research of Baroque musical practices. Titles are largely in German.
  - Books and journals., undated (Box 54)
    Miscellaneous annotated books and periodical issues annotated by Babitz.
  - Books and journals., undated (Box 55)
  - Books and journals., undated (Box 56)
  - Books and Journals, undated (Box 72)
  - Books and journals, undated (Box 73)
  - Books and journals, undated (Box 77)
  - Books and journals, undated (Box 78)
  - Books and journals, undated (Box 79)
  - Books and journals, undated (Box 87)
  - Books and Journals, undated (Box 86)
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
- Correspondence, ca. 1940-1980; Series 7.; 28 boxes (37.5 linear ft.)
  This series consists of personal and professional correspondence relating to early music practice, the EML Bulletin, article submissions, etc.
  - Misc. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Misc. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Misc. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Misc. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 26)
  - Misc. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Misc. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Misc. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Misc. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Misc. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 27)
  - Misc. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Misc. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Misc. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Misc. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Misc. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Misc. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Misc. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Misc. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 29)
  - Misc. (Box 29)
  - Misc. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Misc. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Misc. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Misc. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Misc. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 31)
  - Misc. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Misc. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Misc. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Misc. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Misc. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Misc. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Misc. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Misc. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Misc. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Misc. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Misc. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Misc. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, ca, 1950-1970s (Box 35)
  - Misc. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Misc. (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Misc. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Misc. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Misc. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Misc. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Misc. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Misc. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Misc. (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Misc. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Misc. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Misc. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 40, Folder 6a)
  - Misc. (Box 40, Folder 6b)
  - Misc. (Box 41)
  - Misc. (Box 42)
  - Misc. (Box 43)
  - Misc. (Box 44)
  - Misc. (Box 45)
  - Misc. (Box 46)
  - Misc. (Box 47)
  - Misc. (Box 48)
  - Misc. (Box 49)
  - Misc. (Box 50)
  - Misc. (Box 52)
  - Misc. (Box 53)
- Memorabilia, undated
  - Sol Babitz death mask (Box 92)
  - Autograph book and violin ephemera (Box 83)
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
  - Contents of Babitz's desk (Box 84)
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO MATERIALS: Audio materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
  - Instrument parts, a horn, and a wooden box signed by Paulette E. on November 1979 (Box 85)
- Accession LSC-2002-001 backlog material, LSC-2002-001; 7 Audiovisual Carriers (7 records) (Box 1, Case 2, Box 3A, Box 3B, Box 4)